<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel Experiences on MiruTech</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel Experiences on MiruTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:23:10 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Karnataka Road Trip 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/karnataka-road-trip-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:23:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/karnataka-road-trip-1/</guid>
      <description>Towards the end of December 2023, my parents and I took up this road trip in my Tata Altroz where we visited a few holy shrines and historical places across Karnataka. I’ve written about the trip below and all the expenses mentioned are in INR.&#xA;Plan The plan originated from my mother when I was doing my master’s when she wanted to visit Horanadu Sri Annapoorneshwari temple and the Sringeri Sharadamba temple after I completed my master&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ನಮ್ಮ ಕಾಶಿ ಯಾತ್ರೆ/ಪ್ರವಾಸದ ಸಂಕ್ಷೇಪ ಕಥನ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/varanasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/varanasi/</guid>
      <description>This is an experience written by my grandfather on our trip to Varanasi. Hope you have a good time reading this.&#xA;ನಮ್ಮ ಮೊಮ್ಮಗ ಮುರಳಿಯ ಎಮ್.ಟೆಕ್. ಕಡೆಯ ಅರ್ಧ ವಾರ್ಷಿಕ ಪರೀಕ್ಷೆ ಅಧ್ಯಯನದ ಕಡೆಯಲ್ಲಿ ಪ್ರಾಜೆಕ್ಟ್ ನ ಅಂತರ್ಜಾಲ ಮಂಡನೆಯನ್ನು( ಪಿಪಿಟಿ )13-6-23ಕ್ಕೆ ನಿಗದಿಪಡಿಸಲಾಗಿತ್ತು. ನಂತರ ಕೆಲವು ದಿವಸಗಳ ಬಿಡುವು ಪಡೆದು ಎಲ್ಲಿಗಾದರೂ ಪ್ರವಾಸ ಹೋಗಬೇಕೆಂಬ ಅಪೇಕ್ಷೆಯಿಂದ ತಂದೆ ತಾಯಿಯರೊಡನೆ ಚರ್ಚಿಸಿದಾಗ ದಿಲ್ಲಿ, ಆಗ್ರ, ವಾರಣಾಸಿಯ ಹೆಸರುಗಳು ಪ್ರಸ್ತಾವವಾದವು. ಆಗ ಅವನ ತಾಯಿಯ ಮನಸ್ಸಿನಲ್ಲಿ ನಮ್ಮ ಕಾಶಿಯ ಪ್ರವಾಸವು ಅಲ್ಲಿಯವರೆಗೂ ಕೈಗೂಡದಿರುವುದು ನೆನಪಿಗೆ ಬಂತು. ಕೂಡಲೇ ದೂರವಾಣಿಯ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ತನ್ನ ತಾಯಿಯನ್ನು ವಿಚಾರಿಸಿದಳು.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pondicherry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/pondicherry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 16:57:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/pondicherry/</guid>
      <description>About 15 days have passed since I travelled to Pondicherry with some of my closest friends, bringing back a heart full of memories and a belly full of food. There were 6 of us in 2 vehicles, one of which was a Tata Altroz that had Meghana, Ruthuja, and I. The other was a Nexon EV max with Aniket, Adyanth, and Supriya. All the expenses reported are in INR.&#xA;Plan The idea of us going on a trip originated out of pure coincidence when Adyanth from the US and Meghana from the UK mentioned that they would come to India at the same time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
