<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MiruTech</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MiruTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 16:57:36 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dubai</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 16:57:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/dubai/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a few months after a memorable trip to the financial capital of the UAE and I sit here recalling a trip that contained two of the best things I’ve experienced. I’ve summarized the trip, experiences, and a brief of the expenses incurred.&#xA;Plan I’ve wanted to travel to Dubai ever since a few of my friends travelled there when I was doing my 1st-year B.E. Sometime in May 2024, I realized that if I applied 3 days of leave during the last week of October, I would end up with 9 days of holidays and the same being the shoulder weeks of peak season in Dubai meant it was time the trip happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karnataka Road Trip 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/karnataka-road-trip-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:23:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/karnataka-road-trip-1/</guid>
      <description>Towards the end of December 2023, my parents and I took up this road trip in my Tata Altroz where we visited a few holy shrines and historical places across Karnataka. I’ve written about the trip below and all the expenses mentioned are in INR.&#xA;Plan The plan originated from my mother when I was doing my master’s when she wanted to visit Horanadu Sri Annapoorneshwari temple and the Sringeri Sharadamba temple after I completed my master&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosting on Github</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tech/hosting-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 01:15:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tech/hosting-on-github/</guid>
      <description>This are the steps which I followed to bring up my website.&#xA;mirutech.dev One can get started by building their website on Hugo. From a Windows user perspective, all that needs to be done is download the binary from git and add the location to the environment variables of your systems. Then follow Hugo&amp;rsquo;s quick start guide. In the getting started guide hugo.toml is used, but based on the theme, that I was using, I changed it to config.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ನಮ್ಮ ಕಾಶಿ ಯಾತ್ರೆ/ಪ್ರವಾಸದ ಸಂಕ್ಷೇಪ ಕಥನ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/varanasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/varanasi/</guid>
      <description>This is an experience written by my grandfather on our trip to Varanasi. Hope you have a good time reading this.&#xA;ನಮ್ಮ ಮೊಮ್ಮಗ ಮುರಳಿಯ ಎಮ್.ಟೆಕ್. ಕಡೆಯ ಅರ್ಧ ವಾರ್ಷಿಕ ಪರೀಕ್ಷೆ ಅಧ್ಯಯನದ ಕಡೆಯಲ್ಲಿ ಪ್ರಾಜೆಕ್ಟ್ ನ ಅಂತರ್ಜಾಲ ಮಂಡನೆಯನ್ನು( ಪಿಪಿಟಿ )13-6-23ಕ್ಕೆ ನಿಗದಿಪಡಿಸಲಾಗಿತ್ತು. ನಂತರ ಕೆಲವು ದಿವಸಗಳ ಬಿಡುವು ಪಡೆದು ಎಲ್ಲಿಗಾದರೂ ಪ್ರವಾಸ ಹೋಗಬೇಕೆಂಬ ಅಪೇಕ್ಷೆಯಿಂದ ತಂದೆ ತಾಯಿಯರೊಡನೆ ಚರ್ಚಿಸಿದಾಗ ದಿಲ್ಲಿ, ಆಗ್ರ, ವಾರಣಾಸಿಯ ಹೆಸರುಗಳು ಪ್ರಸ್ತಾವವಾದವು. ಆಗ ಅವನ ತಾಯಿಯ ಮನಸ್ಸಿನಲ್ಲಿ ನಮ್ಮ ಕಾಶಿಯ ಪ್ರವಾಸವು ಅಲ್ಲಿಯವರೆಗೂ ಕೈಗೂಡದಿರುವುದು ನೆನಪಿಗೆ ಬಂತು. ಕೂಡಲೇ ದೂರವಾಣಿಯ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ತನ್ನ ತಾಯಿಯನ್ನು ವಿಚಾರಿಸಿದಳು.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pondicherry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/pondicherry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 16:57:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-experiences/pondicherry/</guid>
      <description>About 15 days have passed since I travelled to Pondicherry with some of my closest friends, bringing back a heart full of memories and a belly full of food. There were 6 of us in 2 vehicles, one of which was a Tata Altroz that had Meghana, Ruthuja, and I. The other was a Nexon EV max with Aniket, Adyanth, and Supriya. All the expenses reported are in INR.&#xA;Plan The idea of us going on a trip originated out of pure coincidence when Adyanth from the US and Meghana from the UK mentioned that they would come to India at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/masters/courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 16:08:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/masters/courses/</guid>
      <description>Background I always had the ambition of doing a master&amp;rsquo;s in the USA and getting into a job was never on my radar after completing my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s. But as life turned out, I got hired by Cypress on July 24th, 2018 and my plan of doing an MS in the US went down the drain. But I did want to get a master&amp;rsquo;s, but how and when wasn&amp;rsquo;t clear yet. After getting into my job, I got to know that Cypress assisted people who wanted to do a corporate M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Photos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 12:54:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-photos/</guid>
      <description>The rendering here is not the greatest yet. I still need to figure out how to make these images here look better. Until then you can open the images in new tabs or download and view them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/generic/my-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:45:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/generic/my-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Podcast Experience So I got asked by IEEE-SJCE to appear in their alumni podcast and damn was it a nice experience and an absolute honor.&#xA;Below is the YouTube Podcast link.&#xA;Let me know your comments and what you feel about it below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/generic/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:21:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/generic/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello World Well, hello there. Thank you for taking the time to visit my website and read my blog. So how did this all start for me? How and where did I get the idea of having my website and starting to write my Blogs on it? Also, what do I intend to do with this?&#xA;This is a small story, to be honest. I came across a section of a YouTube video by Linus Tech Tips where Linus talks about the 3-2-1 strategy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
